Dark Army told me stage two is ready.
I know he's dead. I
know this isn't real.
I think this is the beginning
of a beautiful friendship.
People have been forging paper records.
We haven't set up a system
to verify these sorts of claims.
Rebuilding our database
is the only solution
to this problem.
Immunity is on the table
in exchange for a name.
That's all I care about.
We have to talk to them.
They can't do this after
what happened last night.
What, that some Mexican
restaurant got shot up?
We can't let them get away with this.
They're going to get away with this.
Promise me you'll let
me do the interview.
You've been messing with
me for way too long.
It's my birthday gift to you.
_
You know, of all the gifts he sent,
this is the greatest we ever received.
I have to know what you're planning.
We were meant to be allies.
We might just want the same thing,
and I need to be involved.
I am pretty positive you're dead wrong
about that, my friend.
I don't think there's anything
we could possibly agree on.
Seems you've been very busy lately.
I have to know what you're planning.
We were meant to be allies.
We might just want the same thing,
and I need to be involved.
I'm pretty positive you're dead wrong
about that, my friend.
I don't think there's anything
we could possibly agree on.
I don't know what game you're playing,
but I suggest you cut the bullshit.
If there's nothing else,
I think we're done here.
Aren't you forgetting that I know
your dirty little secret?
There are people close to
you that wouldn't be happy
if they knew what I know.
We're both too smart to allow pettiness
to dictate our actions.
We're better than that.
Weigh the pros and cons.
Do what you need to do.
As soon as the tabulations
are over with,
you'll know that telling
anyone about this
does neither one of us any good.
In fact, you'll realize
that the only thing to do
in your position when it comes to me
is nothing.
Elliot!
I believe in fate.
There's a reason we met.
There's something between us.
I can see it.
You're only seeing
what's in front of you.
You're not seeing what's above you.
I don't understand, I...
I want to.
Help me understand.
"So much depends upon a red wheelbarrow
"glazed with rainwater
beside the white chickens."
My father used to say that to
me all the time as a child.
It was the only English he knew.
Some silly poem.
It meant very much to him.
I use it as a reminder...
a reminder of him
and a reminder of what I
never wanted to become.
- sync and corrections by Caio -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Go on.
How is the Dark Army behind this...
whatever this is?
It's one thing to question your mind.
It's another to question
your eyes and ears.
But then again, isn't it all the same,
our senses just mediocre
inputs for our brain?
Come on.
Sure, we rely on them,
trust they accurately portray
the real world around us,
but what if the haunting
truth is, they can't?
That what we perceive isn't
the real world at all
but just our mind's best guess?
That all we really have
is a garbled reality,
a fuzzy picture we will
never truly make out.
So this is where you've been staying?
God, no. We're only operating from here.
Dark Army set this up?
They're our partners. Of
course they set this up...
for us.
We needed a discreet place.
Discreet? You're the most
wanted man in the world,
and you're walking around like that.
You really don't remember this, do you?
Because I'm not the one who set this up.
We've been through this already.
It must have been him. Mr. Robot.
Elliot...
I need to know.
Are you able to handle this or not?
You're here under great risk, not
only to me, but to our plan.
And your, um... disposition
is very much concerning me.
Joanna.
Your wife.
She's been looking for you.
I'm doing what's necessary.
Thank goodness they've
given us these UPSes
for the power surges.
Ready to look at what we accomplished?
Wanna take your jacket off, hon?
Don't call me hon.
I just meant you have
some blood on there.
I had some too, on my shirt.
I know what's on my fucking jacket.
I'm sorry for the loss of...
I invoke my Fifth Amendment privilege
against self-incrimination
and respectfully decline to
answer any of your questions.
I'm not asking a question.
I just wanted to tell you how
sorry I am for the loss...
I invoke my Fifth Amendment privilege
against self-incrimination
and respectfully decline to
answer any of your questions.
I know you guys were close.
I'm sorry you had to lose him.
He was involved in one of the most
notorious hacker rings in the world.
Things like this come
with the territory.
I invoke my Fifth Amendment privilege
against self-incrimination
and respectfully...
You keep trying to invoke
the Fifth Amendment,
but there's this thing
called the Patriot Act
that a bunch of people signed into law.
You know what that means?
It means that you are
not on some TV show.
This isn't "Burn Notice."
There are no blue skies
for you out there.
Characters like you
are not welcome here.
As far as anyone's concerned right now,
you're an enemy combatant.
You don't have any rights.
What the fuck do you
want me to tell you?
I meet my boyfriend. We go eat.
He gets shot.
End of Q&A.
Give me a sec.
You're gonna want to talk to me.
We're not so different.
We're both Jersey girls.
I know it's hard for you
to believe this right now,
but trust me,
by the end of this day, you and
I are gonna be best friends.
Of all the gifts you've been sending me,
I've got to say,
this one got me the wettest.
So... I'm waiting.
What?
The phone calls...
the gifts.
Make me understand.
I bet you feel all high
and mighty right now.
That right?
Do you think you're a
powerful man, Scott?
Do you feel powerful?
I am the CTO
of the largest conglomerate...
I'm not interested in your job title.
I want to understand
what would make a
powerful man like you...
risk everything...
all so he could drive me crazy?
What does it matter?
The morning I learned that I was
promoted to CTO,
I get the call.
Price wanted to hold an event that night
to announce my position.
I thought,
"I couldn't be any happier."
And then Sharon walked in.
She had made a...
a doctor's visit...
and wanted me to go with her.
She had found out a month ago
she was pregnant.
Didn't talk.
I didn't know if she was...
happy or sad...
or if I was happy or sad.
But when we first saw that sonogram...
We lit up.
I thought, uh...
this is gonna end up being
the best day of my life.
After the funeral, I didn't know why...
I couldn't understand
how I could... gain and
lose everything...
In one fell swoop.
I wanted you to feel what I felt.
I wanted to give you hope
that I could step on!
But I'm sorry.
Ohh...
You pussy.
You piece of shit.
I hope you rot in hell like your wife.
You're mourning a woman
who, after she found out
she was pregnant, was gonna
fuck my husband's brains out.
I'm glad she's dead.
Fuck her and her fetus corpse.
Aah!
No wonder your
wife was gonna cheat on you.
You're weak and pathetic.
That child's lucky to be dead.
No...
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, what have I done?
My God...
911. What's your emergency?
Vincent had a punctured lung
and a broken collarbone,
but the doctors say he's gonna recover.
The bad news is, he's gonna be arrested
and put away for a long
time for his stunt in D.C.
God.
Politicians love to
teabag the rest of us.
Too bad they can't take the heat.
What your friend did
was domestic terrorism
in the eyes of the law.
Not my friend.
His associates, the ones we arrested,
identified you as the
ringleader of their outfit.
Trust me,
I am no leader.
I can barely keep a guy.
Look, Darlene.
I don't really care
what happened in D.C.
In fact, I thought it was kind of funny.
I've never seen Congress move as
fast as they did on that day.
But there are serious
holes in your story.
And I want to work with
you to figure out why.
Look.
Babe.
I know how this works.
You get close to me,
play the sympathy card,
relate to me...
we're just two crazy,
wacky Jersey girls.
Take advantage that I did lose
what probably was the love of my life.
And you act like you care.
But that's just it...
an act.
Which is sick and twisted.
I'd rather you arrest me
and throw me into jail.
But let's get something straight.
You will not get anything out of me.
So why don't you go read your manual
and find the chapter on conniving cunts
that don't give a fuck
about you or your feelings
and then get back to me
with some real tactics?
Otherwise, get me a lawyer.
As far as I'm concerned,
my only statement to you
is that I saw my boyfriend
go brainless last night at dinner.
I ordered the breakfast combo,
and he stole some of my bacon.
If you want any other details,
the answer is suck a dick.
Wait here.
Remember that movie?
I used to love it growing up.
It's not really scary, but gory.
You know how those two things
aren't really the same?
This is the stuff we found
from Cisco's place.
Couldn't find any tapes.
Figured you were smart
enough to destroy them.
We're running fingerprints and DNA.
Soon we're gonna figure out
if those fsociety videos
were filmed using this camera.
If we find your DNA on that stuff...
I don't know...
you tell me how that looks.
As far as your fsociety
videos are concerned,
it looks like the one
person that can help you
is fucking dead.
As far as I'm concerned,
Cisco and I were into
filming some freaky shit.
Is that a matter of
national security too, hon?
Then there's this.
Remember your buddy, Xander Jones?
According to him, you guys
had a sexual relationship.
Dude, are you just gonna
slut shame me all day?
Is that really all you got?
He also said that you were
the one that stole his gun.
Well, I can't prove that, obviously,
because your fingerprints
weren't on his safe.
I figured you'd be crafty
enough to clean up afterward.
What is funny, though,
is that this casing is linked
to the Fun Society arcade.
Darlene...
You sure you still don't
want to talk to me?
What do you think?
They're planning something.
Mr. Robot, Tyrell, Dark
Army, and Whiterose
are in cahoots to plan something big.
And the worst part?
They all think it's me.
They all think I'm the ringleader,
the one in charge,
and I have no idea what it is.
This place is Mount Olympus.
We are prime.
We're ready!
These are blueprints for a building
and a disassembled firmware
for an uninterruptible power supply,
but I can't understand much past that.
I'm not sure what the play is.
I could ask him,
but who am I really asking?
Elliot, look over here.
Paper docs are coming in from all over,
slowly but surely.
The blueprints.
Is that the building?
The offline version?
17 of 71 facilities around
the country so far.
Within the next month,
they'll have all the
paper documents here.
I thought we were gonna have to
deal with multiple facilities,
but they're making it easier for
us by moving it all to one.
This is where the paper
records are going.
They're trying to rebuild the database.
Titles and deeds, the bloodline
of all real property
in this country.
This is how they're surviving the hack.
When our malware executes,
their whole program...
Our malware?
What malware?
Oh, you orchestrated it beautifully.
When the hacked firmware...
Designed to override the safety limits
on the UPS devices
and overcharge the lead acid
batteries in the battery room...
filling the space up with hydrogen gas.
After breaking the fans and
cutting off backup power,
the malicious firmware
repeatedly re-engages the
UPS autotransformer,
creating a spark to ignite an explosion.
There are enough batteries to
produce enough hydrogen gas
to level the building.
When you hacked Evil Corp,
you gave us access to the backdoor.
You made it possible
for us to infect them.
I coded the femtocell
malware for Darlene.
But it wasn't supposed to be for this.
The conference call leak, I must admit,
was quite cute... a nice distraction.
But this...
is for us.
All of us.
I'm gonna rip his fuckin' face off!
This fucker thinks he can hurt my girl.
What's his address?
Tell me his address, 'cause
I'm gonna go find him,
and I'm gonna fuckin' kill him.
Are you done?
If you're serious about punishing him...
I am. I am.
Just tell me what to do,
and I'll fuckin' do it.
I'll do it.
No questions asked.
- Just...
- Shh.
If you are serious about punishing him,
then you can do one thing for me.
What? Anything. Say the word.
You remember the night we met
at the E Corp party?
Yeah.
You were tending the bar that night.
You stayed late to clean up.
Yeah, that's what we
always do after the...
Then you saw Scott
coming down from the stairwell
leading to the roof.
He was disheveled, out
of breath, sweaty.
You were about to ask him
if he needed anything,
but he was in such a hurry, he
left without saying a word.
What are you talking about?
I didn't see anything like that.
Yes, you did.
No.
I remember because the cops
were asking every one of us
questions about that night,
and like I told them...
cleaned up my station, and I went home.
Derek, you said you were
serious about punishing him.
Yeah, but Joanna...
Look at my face, Derek.
You want the man that did this to me
to do what he did and get away with it?
But Joanna, I...
Once you tell the cops your story,
they're gonna ask you why
you're just now confessing
after months of silence.
You're gonna tell them
that you were scared...
that Scott Knowles intimidated you.
That when Tyrell went missing,
you didn't think any of
that mattered anymore.
But your conscience got
the better of you.
This is how we win.
This is how we punish him.
You understand?
Thank you.
Thank you for protecting me.
Of course, babe. I love you.
Now, let's go over it again.
- We can't do this.
- You want us to stay on target?
This is the target. This
gets us to the top.
I know we've been operating
under top secret
on this program, but I
think it's worth the risk.
This girl's being a wise-ass.
She thinks she's smarter than we are.
That's because so far she has been.
We got to show her we're smarter.
Unless she thinks we're worthy,
none of this is gonna fly.
Just trying to sidestep
the mines, like you said.
We've been building this
plan for three months.
Look around you.
All our leads are getting
killed and disappearing.
We've lost three suspects.
Dark Army's cleaning house.
So that must mean something
is about to go down.
Our window is closing.
Every lead we've been
following up to this point
has led to a dead end.
Yeah, I'm gonna bring
the ADIC in on this.
Please, you're gonna let
him try and flip her?
She's gonna shut down.
I'm right for this.
Then I'm gonna go in with you.
Let me do it alone.
I know her.
I am her.
And if we're doing this,
we're doing this now.
We have 6,332 agents
working on just this case alone.
It's the hardest case
I've ever worked on
and probably the hardest
one I ever will.
Swear to God, the only reason
why I think I've gotten this far...
Is because I have no life.
It's the only thing I've
been able to think about.
Now I'm sitting here with you...
In this awful room.
And no matter what story gets
written in the final analysis,
we've both been a part
of one of the biggest
events in world history.
Believe what you want.
But neither you nor I
are special.
I've already learned that lesson.
If you're open to changing your mind,
I'd like to show you something.
Come with me.
You're a lot more
special than you think.
Sure, the strategy was risky, but...
we knew we only had one shot.
If we rounded everyone up, guns blazing,
we thought we would never
get the man in the middle.
And with the stakes being this high,
it was imperative that we got him
before he knew we were getting him.
So we sat back
and waited.
They call it the python approach.
They'll lie in wait
for the right moment to strike.
You know some can go up
to a year without eating?
The patient predator.
And then Romero's death
made you all scurry.
Funny enough, you thought
Dark Army was involved.
As it turns out, it was
just a stray bullet
from the neighbor next door.
Freak accident.
You've got to be fucking kidding me.
I've tried everything.
I fought him. I OD'd on Adderall.
I made peace with him. I
even got myself arrested.
No matter what I do,
he always finds a way.
Why?
That's all I want to know.
Why is it so important
for you to torment me?
What is it that you care so much about?
What's this all for?
I'm not tormenting you.
After everything you've put me through,
you continue to lie?
I didn't lie to you.
He's alive, man!
He's sitting right fucking there!
You made a plan with the Dark Army.
When was that?
The night of the hack?
What is stage two?
The femtocell, the backdoor?
You planned all of that with him?
You can't look at it like this.
You're me. I'm you.
You figured that out.
We're the same guy.
Everything you're blaming me for
you're blaming yourself for.
Stop talking in circles.
You got Whiterose to
get us out of prison.
The release... that was you.
You somehow communicated with them.
It's what you wanted.
You said to Darlene before
we started this thing
that we had to go all the way.
It was all part of the plan.
Otherwise, what was the
point of the hack?
If we were going to do this,
we had to go all the way.
And that, Elliot, is what I want.
It's what you asked me here for.
Then tell me, what is that, exactly?
What is "all the way"?
This is where we get into trouble.
You're meant to know only
as much as you can handle.
When you wander outside of your realm
is when we end up fighting.
Are you...
you distracting me right now?
What are you doing?
I'm hacking the firmware
like we discussed.
We didn't discuss shit.
We're not hacking anything.
This will level that
building and kill people.
Elliot, you need to leave
that computer alone.
- I'm confused.
- It's over.
I'm deleting the malware.
Elliot, I wouldn't do that.
You can't delete that.
Not only am I gonna delete it,
I'm gonna get rid of the backdoor.
You do that, and everything
we worked for is gone.
Elliot, I am warning you...
This isn't what I want.
I want it shut down.
But this was your idea.
Leave the computer alone!
He's not gonna let you do this.
Trust me.
I don't know what's gotten into you.
We're supposed to be gods together,
and yet you want to destroy our destiny?
You're not making sense.
Elliot, listen to him.
Walk away from the computer.
You're the same.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
We are definitely not the same!
Back away from the computer.
This is just another of Mr.
Robot's mind tricks.
No.
Elliot...
I don't want to shoot you, but I will.
Elliot, listen to him.
He's not holding a gun.
He's not even there.
Elliot, you need to listen to him
and step away from the computer!
Touch that keyboard,
and I will shoot you.
No.
He won't.
He can't.
He doesn't exist.
I'm the only one that exists.
It's time to finally take back control.
Real control.
Ah...
You know, when you gave me this,
you said to stop anyone who
gets in the way of our plan.
I didn't know what you meant,
but now it's very clear.
You did this to yourself, Elliot.
You asked earlier what "all the way" is.
This is it.
Sorry, kiddo.
I couldn't
let anyone stop this...
including us.
Thanks for staying with us, Codyites.
There's a lot to get to tonight.
Look, all we do here is...
is we try and bring you the truth.
And they're trying to take that away.
They
tried to take it away.
Some of you might notice your
lights flickering tonight.
Now, the fa...
Hello?
Don't worry. It's Angela.
Tyrell?
Tyrell, are you there?
It's okay.
They told me you would be calling.
This is a secure line.
Are you with Elliot right now?
Yes.
Okay, I'm on my way.
Don't let anyone near him.
I should be the first person
he sees when he wakes up.
Okay.
Tyrell, you did what needed to be done.
I love him.
I do too.
♪
Both of us lonely ♪
Have you given any more
thought to what I said?
I don't want to discuss this.
- Mobley...
- Fredrick.
Seriously, Fredrick,
what if we could?
This might work.
And also, it might not.
I've taken enough risks
for one lifetime.
I don't want to discuss it anymore.
But what if we could
generate the keys...
Tanya...
Will you just please shut up?
What? This is important.
- We need to talk about it.
- Change the subject.
I don't want to change the subject.
I miss my family.
I don't want to live here.
Oh, come on, it's nice out here.
You know, uh... look,
no more bad winters.
Hardly rains. That's great.
I hate your friend. He's a dick.
No, I-I told you.
He did not know you
were in the bathroom.
Trust me, he knew exactly
what he was doing.
Weirdo. Save up enough money,
and you'll be able to get
your own place eventually.
Okay? Apartments here are dirt cheap.
Won't be that long.
Just be thankful he was
able to get us this job.
Hey, what flavor did you get again?
You want to trade?
Please, just look at it.
Okay, so... so what? Say I did.
Then what?
If what I discovered is real,
do you know what that means?
Yeah, I know exactly what it means.
Yeah. It means we could
potentially undo this whole thing.
Put everything back the way it was.
I know. I know.
Please.
Just look at what I found.
Excuse me.
Oh, sorry, dude. We're on a break.
Yeah, I just had a quick question.
Do you have the time?
- sync and corrections by Caio -
- www.addic7ed.com -
www.tvsubtitles.net